bangmybfs.com 2015-06-11

# 

## Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

**Disclaimer & Privacy Policy**

**Disclaimer**

This website is owned by SISTEMAS INFORMATICOS ESPABIT S. L. (from now on ESPABIT) and is in compliance with the Law 34/2002 of July 11, LSSI (Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce), the Royal Decree-Law 13/2012 of 30 March, as well as the obligation to inform the user referred to Law 15/1999 of December 13 (Protection of Personal Data)

**Identifying Data**  
SISTEMAS INFORMATICOS ESPABIT S. L.   
CIF: B97979710   
PO Box 28, 46520   
Puerto de Sagunto (Valencia)   
Tel: 902 909 246   
Registered in the Commercial Registry of Valencia, volume 36363, Book 6145, page 74, sheet V-128046, 1st entry 

For notifications and in compliance with LSSI, our contact address is: 

SISTEMAS INFORMATICOS ESPABIT S. L.  
Av. Jerónimo Roure 49, 2ºB  
Pol. Industrial Ingruinsa  
Puerto de Sagunto 46520 (VALENCIA)

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to the site bangmychick.com and all other sites owned or controlled by Espabit ("the Company") and in which this policy appears. As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it.  
**Adults Only Service** ** ** ****

**THIS IS AN ADULTS   _ONLY_  SERVICE**. We will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Sites; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person.    

**Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety** ** ** ****  
Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system. 

**Information We Collect From You** ** ** ****  
During sign up we require that you provide us with certain information which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, and password), Financial Data (i.e., credit card/billing information). Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history.    

**How is this Information Used?** ** ** ****  
Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors as necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.   
We may use cookies and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in.   
We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites.    

**You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third Parties** ** ** ****  
We process credit card transactions via industry standard encryption through third party processors, which processors only use your information for that purpose. Financial Data is considered private information and will not be shared by us with third parties except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding by you that such transaction(s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party. Financial or other Data provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on the Sites or in response to emails sent to you by the Sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party's terms and conditions and privacy policy.    

**Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address** ** ** ****  
Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to the Sites. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us please unsubscribe by sending us an email to [info@espabit.com](mailto:info@espabit.com). We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent.  **Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Sites.**  

**Advertisements**  

We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or action tags to measure advertising effectiveness on an anonymous basis. Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Sites on such advertisers' website(s).    
Changes to the Privacy Policy   
We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.    
Changes in the Ownership of the Sites
